RG 001:010, Connecticut Archives
Connecticut State Library
- Foreign correspondence, 1st series, 1661-1748
  - With British government. Part 2, documents 84-170, 1663-1748 (Volume 1 / 53)
  - 1661-1732 (Volume 2 / 54)
- Foreign correspondence, 2nd series, 1666-1748
    The index for the 2nd series begins on page 147.
  - Records, 1666-1748 (Box 43)
- Indians, 1st series, 1647-1789
  - Part 1, documents 1-133, 1647-1745 (Volume 1 / 55)
  - Part 2, documents 134-265, 1647-1745 (Volume 2 / 56)
  - 1746-1789 (Volume 2 / 57)
- Indians, 2nd series, 1666-1820
  - Brooklyn Indians; Sequonnock Indians (Volume 1 / 58)
  - Sequonnock Indians; Tunxis Indians; Indian affairs (Volume 2 / 59)
- Industry, 1st series, 1647-1789
  - 1708-1763 (Volume 1 / 60)
  - 1764-1789 (Volume 2 / 61)
- Industry, 2nd series, 1747-1820
  - Agriculture; manufactures (Volume 1 / 62)
  - Manufactures; mines and mining (Volume 2 / 63)
  - Fish and fisheries (Volume 3 / 64)
- Insolvent debtors, 1st series, 1762-1787
  - 1762-1787 (Volume 1 / 65)
- Insolvent debtors, 2nd series, 1750-1820
  - Records, 1750-1820 (Box 43-49)
- Lotteries and divorces, 1st series, 1755-1789
  - 1755-1789 (Volume 1 / 66)
- Lotteries and divorces, 2nd series, 1750-1820
  - Records, 1750-1820 (Box 50)
- Militia, 1st series, 1678-1757
  - 1678-1729 (Volume 1 / 67)
  - 1730-1740 (Volume 2 / 68)
  - 1740-1746 (Volume 3 / 69)
  - 1747-1752 (Volume 4 / 70)
  - 1752-1757 (Volume 5 / 71)
- Militia, 2nd series, 1747-1786
  - 1749-1759 (Volume 1 / 72)
  - 1760-1761 (Volume 2 / 73)
  - 1762-1763 (Volume 3 / 74)
  - 1764-1766 (Volume 4 / 75)
  - 1767-1768 (Volume 5 / 76)
  - 1769 (Volume 6 / 77)
  - 1770 (Volume 7 / 78)
  - 1771 (Volume 8 / 79)
  - 1772 (Volume 9 / 80)
  - 1773-1774 (Volume 10 / 81)
  - 1775 (Volume 11 / 82)
  - 1776 (Volume 12 / 83)
  - 1777-1778 (Volume 13 / 84)
  - 1779-1780 (Volume 14 / 85)
  - 1781-1783 (Volume 15 / 86)
  - 1784-1788 (Volume 16 / 87)
- Militia, 3rd series, 1728-1820
  - Public acts, 1741-1815 (Volume 1 / 88)
  - Public acts; miscellaneous, 1816-1820 (Volume 2 / 89)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1728-1790 (Volume 3 / 90)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1791-1792 (Volume 4 / 91)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1793-1794 (Volume 5 / 92)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1795-1796 (Volume 6 / 93)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1797-1798 (Volume 7 / 94)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1799-1800 (Volume 8 / 95)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1801-1802 (Volume 9 / 96)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1803-1804 (Volume 10 / 97)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1805-1806 (Volume 11 / 98)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1807-1808 (Volume 12 / 99)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1809-1810 (Volume 13 / 100)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1811-1812 (Volume 14 / 101)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1813-1814 (Volume 15 / 102)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1815-1816 (Volume 16 / 103)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1817-1818 (Volume 17 / 104)
  - Officers and formation of regiments, 1819-1820 (Volume 18 / 105)
- Miscellaneous, 1st series, 1635-1789
  - Gov. Andross; Connecticut and New Haven commissioners; appeals to England; etc. Part 1, documents 1-88 (Volume 1 / 106)
  - Gov. Andross; Connecticut and New Haven commissioners; appeals to England; etc. Part 2, documents 89-214 (Volume 1 / 107)
  - Slaves, 1691-1761; houses burnt; smallpox; inquests; briefs; etc. Part 1, documents 1-150 (Volume 2 / 108)
  - Slaves, 1691-1761; houses burnt; smallpox; inquests; briefs; etc. Part 2, documents 151-337 (Volume 2 / 109)
  - Houses burnt; New Haven State House; counties; sheriffs; etc. Part 1, documents 1-175 (Volume 3 / 109)
  - Houses burnt; New Haven State House; counties; sheriffs; etc. Part 2, documents 176-341 (Volume 3 / 110)
- Miscellaneous, 2nd series, 1686-1820
  - Sickness; slavery, 1750-1820 (Volume 1 / 112)
  - Washington Memorial; maps; lotteries; pooor (Volume 2 / 113)
- Private controversies, 1st series, 1642-1717
  - 1642-1682 (Volume 1 / 114)
  - 1682-1684 (Volume 2 / 115)
  - 1685-1687 (Volume 3 / 116)
  - 1689-1696 (Volume 4 / 117)
  - 1697-1701 (Volume 5 / 118)
  - 1702-1716 (Volume 6 / 119)
- Private controversies, 2nd series, 1636-1811
  - Records, 1636-1811 (Box 51-66)
- Revolutionary War, 1st series, 1763-1789
  - Part 1, documents 1-202, 1775 (Volume 1 / 120)
    Includes Stamp Act, etc., 1764-1767
  - Part 1, documents 203-440, 1775 (Volume 1 / 121)
  - Muster rolls, 1775 (Volume 2 / 122)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 1, documents 1-279, 1775 (Volume 3 / 123)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 280-666, 1775 (Volume 3 / 124)
  - Part 1, documents 1-209, 1776 (Volume 4 / 125)
  - Part 2, documents 210-430, 1776 (Volume 4 / 126)
  - Part 1, documents 1-251, 1776 (Volume 5 / 127)
  - Part 2, documents 252-475, 1776 (Volume 5 / 128)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 1-290, 1775-1777 (Volume 6 / 129)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 291-552, 1775-1777 (Volume 6 / 130)
  - 1777 (Volume 7 / 131)
  - Part 1, documents 1-197, 1777-1778 (Volume 8 / 132)
  - Part 2, documents 198-405, 1777-1778 (Volume 8 / 133)
  - Vessels, 1776-1778 (Volume 9 / 134)
  - 1778 (Volume 10 / 135)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 1, documents 1-282, 1777-1778 (Volume 11 / 136)
  - Soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 283-649, 1777-1778 (Volume 11 / 137)
  - 1778 (Volume 12 / 138)
  - 1778-1779 (Volume 13 / 139)
  - 1779 (Volume 14 / 140)
  - 1779-1780 (Volume 15 / 141)
  - Pay table, soldiers and accounts. Part 1, documents 1-289, 1779-1780 (Volume 16 / 142)
  - Pay table, soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 290-628, 1778-1780 (Volume 16 / 143)
  - Pay table, soldiers and accounts. Part 1, documents 1-254, 1780-1781 (Volume 17 / 144)
  - Pay table, soldiers and accounts. Part 2, documents 255-342, 1780-1781 (Volume 17 / 145)
  - Part 1, documents 1-188, 1780 (Volume 18 / 146)
  - Part 2, documents 189-408, 1780 (Volume 18 / 147)
  - Part 1, documents 1-211, 1780 (Volume 19 / 148)
  - Part 2, documents 212-451, 1780 (Volume 19 / 149)
  - 1780-1781 (Volume 20 / 150)
  - 1781 (Volume 21 / 151)
  - 1782 (Volume 22 / 152)
  - 1782 (Volume 23 / 153)
  - 1783 (Volume 24 / 154)
  - Pay table, soldiers. Part 1, documents 1-262, 1781-1783 (Volume 25 / 155)
  - Pay table, soldiers. Part 2, documents 263-535, 1781-1783 (Volume 25 / 156)
  - 1783-1784 (Volume 26 / 157)
  - Part 1, documents 1-183, 1784 (Volume 27 / 158)
  - Part 1, documents 184-395, 1784 (Volume 27 / 159)
  - Part 1, documents 1-174, 1784-1785 (Volume 28 / 160)
  - Part 2, documents 175-366, 1784-1785 (Volume 28 / 161)
  - 1785-1786 (Volume 29 / 162)
  - Connecticut line. Part 1, documents 1-50, 1771-1782 (Volume 30 / 163)
  - Connecticut line. Part 1, documents 1-50, 1777-1782 (Volume 30 / 163)
  - Connecticut line. Part 2, documents 51-167, 1777-1782 (Volume 30 / 164)
  - Soldiers; vessels; prisoners; letters. Part 1, documents 1-194 (Volume 31 / 165)
  - Soldiers; vessels; prisoners; letters. Part 2, documents 195-406 (Volume 31 / 166)
  - 177-1788 (Volume 32 / 167)
  - 1777-1788 (Volume 33 / 168)
  - 1780-1788 (Volume 34 / 169)
  - 1775-1787 (Volume 35 / 170)
  - Miscellaneous. Part 1, documents 1-186, 1787-1788 (Volume 36 / 171)
  - Miscellaneous. Part 2, documents 187-370, 1787-1788 (Volume 36 / 172)
  - Slaves, 1764-1789 (Volume 37 / 173)
- Revolutionary War, 2nd series, 1756-1786
  There is no complete index for this series.
  - Rolls and lists, Regiments 1-8, 1780 (Volume 1 / 174)
    Also numbered 38 as a continuation of 1st series numbering.
  - Rolls and lists, Col. S. B. Webb, 1780-1783 (Volume 2 / 175)
    Also numbered 39 as a continuation of 1st series numbering.
  - Receipts; rolls and accounts, 1777-1788 (Volume 3 / 176)
    Also numbered 40 as a continuation of 1st series numbering.
  - Miscellaneous; rolls and accounts, 1776-1782 (Volume 4 / 177)
    Also numbered 41 as a continuation of 1st series numbering.
  - Loyalists accounts; militia, 1775-1808 (Volume 5 / 178)
  - Family supplies, 1780-1786 (Volume 6 / 179)
  - Pay tables, 1775-1782 (Volume 7 / 180)
  - Haskell's receipts, Vol. 1, 1777-1788 (Volume 8 / 181)
  - Haskell's receipts, Vol. 2, 1777-1788 (Volume 9 / 182)
  - Regimental accounts, Vol. 1, 1775-1783 (Volume 10 / 183)
  - Regimental accounts, VOl. 2, 1775-1783 (Volume 11 / 184)
  - Connecticut line, Vol. 1, 1780-1788 (Volume 12 / 185)
  - Connecticut line, Vol. 2, 1780-1788 (Volume 13 / 186)
  - Invalid certificates, Vol. 1, 1782-1792 (Volume 14 / 187)
  - Invalid certificates, Vol. 2, 1782-1792 (Volume 15 / 188)
  - Invalid certificates, Vol. 3, 1782-1791 (Volume 16 / 189)
  - Half-pay certofocates, 1776-1788 (Volume 17 / 190)
  - Ledger, 1780-1783 (Volume 18 / 191)
  - Redfield's refreshment accounts, 1781 (Volume 19 / 192)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 1, 1775-1777 (Volume 20 / 193)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 2, 1777-1778 (Volume 21 / 194)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 3, 1778-1780 (Volume 22 / 195)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 4, 1778-1783 (Volume 23 / 196)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 5, 1778-1787 (Volume 24 / 197)
  - Pay table journal, Vol. 6, 1778-1795 (Volume 25 / 198)
  - Journal, 1775; Hemp bounty, 1812-1815; Executions, 1817-1831 (Volume 26 / 199)
  - Pay table ledger, Vol. 1, 1775-1781 (Volume 27 / 200)
  - Pay table ledger, Vol. 2, 1775-1784 (Volume 28 / 201)
  - Pay table ledger, Vol. 3, 1779-1785 (Volume 29 / 202)
  - Pay table ledger, Vol. 4, 1783-1792 (Volume 30 / 203)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 1, 1780-1795 (Volume 31 / 204)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 2, 1780-1795 (Volume 32 / 205)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 3, 1780-1795 (Volume 33 / 206)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 4, 1780-1795 (Volume 34 / 207)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 5, 1780-1795 (Volume 35 / 208)
  - Army accounts, Vol. 6, 1780-1795 (Volume 36 / 209)
  - Payments, sundry regiments, 1775-1781 (Volume 37 / 210)
  - Short levies accounts, 1781-1782 (Volume 38 / 211)
  - Accounts with towns, 1776-1783 (Volume 39 / 212)
  - Provisions accounts, 1779-1783 (Volume 40 / 213)
  - Accounts with the United States, Vol. 1, 1786-1791 (Volume 41 / 214)
  - Acocunts with the United States, Vol. 2, 1786-1791 (Volume 42 / 215)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 1, 1775-1776 (Volume 43 / 216)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 2, 1776-1777 (Volume 44 / 217)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 3, 1777-1779 (Volume 45 / 218)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 4, 1779-1781 (Volume 46 / 219)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 5, 1781 (Volume 47 / 220)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 6, 1782-1783 (Volume 48 / 219)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 7, 1783-1784 (Volume 49 / 222)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 8, 1784-1786 (Volume 50 / 223)
  - Pay table waste books, Vol. 9, 1786-1793 (Volume 51 / 224)
  - Account book of Elijah Hubbard, sub-clothier, 1781-1787 (Volume 52 / 225)
  - Ammunitions and provisions, Treasurer John Lawrence; Miscellanous, 1773-1788 (Volume 53 / 226)
  - State militia, 1775-1790, Canaan, Canterbury, Groton, Simsbury, Southington, Woodstock (Volume 54 / 227)
  - Miscellaneous, 1770-1856; Collections of Jessie S. Harrison, Charles E. Jackson, O.T. King, Shadrach Osborn, Anna Morris Perry (Volume 55 / 228)
  - Rolls, commissions, correspondence, miscellaneous, 1774-1834 (Volume 56 / 229)
    Photostat copy
- Revolutionary War, 3rd series, 1765-1820
  - Army and Navy; defense of the state; taxation; loyalists (Volume 1 / 230)
  - Confiscated estates (Volume 2 / 231)
  - Pensions; relief for disabled soldiers;; private claims and petitions: Abner-Guthrie (Volume 3 / 232)
  - Private claims and petitions: Hall-Pearmann (Volume 4 / 233)
  - Private claims and petitions: Peck-Young (Volume 5 / 234)
  - Miscellaneous (Volume 6 / 235)
- Susquehanna settlers, 1755-1796, and Western lands, 1783-1789, 1st series
  - Records (Volume 1 / 236)
- Susquehanna settlers, 1771-1797, and Western lands, 1783-1819, 2nd series
  - Records (Volume 2 / 237)
- Towns and lands, 1st series, 1629-1789
  - Part 1, documents 1-93, before 1695 (Volume 1 / 238)
  - Part 2, documents 54-246, before 1695 (Volume 1 / 239)
  - to 1713 (Volume 2 / 240)
  - to 1723 (Volume 3 / 241)
  - to 1727 (Volume 4 / 242)
  - to 1730 (Volume 5 / 243)
  - to 1738 (Volume 6 / 244)
  - Part 1, documents 1-148, to 1758 (Volume 7 / 245)
  - Part 1, documents 149-307, to 1758 (Volume 7 / 246)
  - Part 1, documents 1-160, to 1762 (Volume 8 / 247)
  - Part 2, documents 161-333, to 1762 (Volume 8 / 248)
  - to 1786 (Volume 9 / 249)
  - to 1790 (Volume 10 / 250)
- Towns and lands, 2nd series, 1649-1820
  - Towns: Ashford-Derby (Volume 1 / 251)
  - Towns: Durham-Killingworth (Volume 2 / 252)
  - Towns: Lebanon-North Stonington (Volume 3 / 253)
  - Towns: Norwalk-Stonington (Volume 4 / 254)
  - Towns: Stratford-Woodstock (Volume 5 / 255)
- Trade and maritime affairs, 1st series, 1668-1789
  - Part 1, documents 1-101, 1668-1751 (Volume 1 / 256)
  - Part 2, documents 102-233, 1668-1751 (Volume 1 / 257)
  - Part 1, documents 1-142, 1752-1789 (Volume 2 / 258)
  - Part 2, documents 143-323, 1752-1789 (Volume 2 / 259)
- Trade and maritime affairs, 2nd series, 1685-1820
  - Rivers and harbors (Volume 1 / 260)
  - Canals; interstate commerce; miscellaneous (Volume 2 / 261)
- Travel, highways, ferries, bridges and taverns, 1st series, 1700-1788
  - Part 1, documents 1-169, 1700-1750 (Volume 1 / 262)
  - Part 2, documents 170-300, 1750-1750 (Volume 1 / 263)
  - Part 1, documents 1-153, 1751-1769 (Volume 2 / 264)
  - Part 2, documents 154-375, 1751-1769 (Volume 2 / 265)
  - 1770-1788 (Volume 3 / 266)
- Travel, highways, ferries, bridges and taverns, 2nd series, 1737-1820
  - Bridges, part 1: public acts; towns, A-Hartford (Volume 1 / 267)
  - Bridges, part 2: towns, Hartford-New Milford (Volume 2 / 267)
  - Bridges, part 3: towns, Newtown-Z (Volume 3 / 269)
  - Ferries: public acts; towns, A-W (Volume 4 / 270)
  - Highways, part 1: public acts; towns, A-Haddam (Volume 5 / 271)
  - Highways, part 2: towns, Hartford-W (Volume 6 / 272)
  - Stage and post roads: public acts; towns, A-W (Volume 7 / 273)
  - Taverns: public acts; towns, A-W (Volume 7 / 273)
  - Turnpikes, part 1: public acts; towns, A-B (Volume 8 / 274)
  - Turnpikes, part 2: towns, C-Derby (Volume 9 / 275)
  - Turnpikes, part 3: towns, Dragon Turnpike-Goshen (Volume 10 / 276)
  - Turnpikes, part 4: towns, Granby-Hartford (Volume 11 / 277)
  - Turnpikes, part 5: towns, Hartford-Middle Road (Volume 12 / 278)
  - Turnpikes, part 6: towns, Middlesex-New Haven (Volume 13 / 279)
  - Turnpikes, part 7: towns, New Haven-Norwich (Volume 14 / 280)
  - Turnpikes, part 15: towns, O-Southbury (Volume 15 / 281)
  - Turnpikes, part 16: towns, Stonington-Tolland County (Volume 16 / 282)
  - Turnpikes, part 17: towns, Torrington-W (Volume 17 / 283)
- War of 1812, 1812-1819
  - Legislation; Governor's messages; Council of Safety; milita (Volume 1 / 301)
  - Commissioners; paymaster; O.M. Gen'ls; Treasury; U.S. accounts; claims; petitions (Volume 2 / 303)
  - Claims; petitions; minors; coast defense; shipping; General Assembly; Conventionl; testimonials (Volume 3 / 303)